Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
[♪♪♪]
MARIA [SIGHS]: Nick. this was a
tragedy. but it's not why we're here.
What. are we fighting
the weather now?
Locals say the cyclone
had a face.
People see things
when they're under stress.
That does not mean
that this is the start
to some other
big world-ending...
[PANTS]
Who are you?
[ROARS]
You don't want
any part of this.
♪ And I... ♪
♪ Will always love you. ooh ♪
♪ Will always love you ♪
♪ You ♪
♪ My darling. you... ♪
♪ Mm-mm ♪
♪ Bittersweet ♪
♪ Memories ♪
♪ That is all ♪
♪ I'm taking ♪
♪ With me ♪
♪ And I ♪
♪ Will always love you ♪
♪ I will always ♪
♪ Love you ♪
♪ I. I will always ♪
Gone.
but not forgotten.
Thanks to Kenneth Lim
and Vihaan Ramamurthy
for their help with that
touching video tribute.
This year has been
nothing short of...
[BLEEP] is crazy.
It's. like. insane.
- Jason.
- What?
No swearing.
It's the last day of school.
We're good.
Historic.
Over five years ago.
half of all life
in the universe.
including our own
Midtown High...
- [SCREAMING]
- ...was wiped from existence.
Then eight months ago.
a band of brave heroes
brought us back.
- [SCREAMING]
- [TUBA BLARES]
They called it "the Blip."
Those of us who Blipped away
came back the same age...
But our classmates
that didn't Blip
had grown five years older.
Yeah. my little brother
is now older than me.
Yeah. it's math.
Even though we had Blipped away
halfway through the school year
and had already taken midterms.
the school made us
start the year
over from the beginning.
It's totally unfair.
It's not right.
- [SIGHS] Tigers...
- [TIGER GROWLS]
...it's been
a long. dramatic.
somewhat
confusing road.
As we draw this year
to a close.
it's time to move on...
to a new phase
of our lives.
Pray nothing crazy
happens again
because are the Avengers
a thing anymore?
Does anyone even have a plan?
I have a plan.
First. I'm gonna sit
next to MJ on the flight.
Second. I'm gonna buy
a dual headphone adapter
and watch movies with her
the whole time.
- Okay.
- Three.
when we go to Venice.
Venice is famous
- for making stuff out of glass.
- True.
I'm gonna buy her
a black dahlia necklace
because her favorite flower
is the black dahlia
- because of. well...
- The murder.
The murder.
Four. when we go to Paris.
I'm gonna take her
to the top of the Eiffel Tower.
- give her the necklace.
- Oh.
Then. five.
I'm gonna tell her how I feel.
Then. six.
hopefully she tells me
she feels
the same way.
Oh. don't forget
step seven.
- Step seven?
- Don't do any of that.
Why?
We're gonna be
bachelors in Europe.
- Ned.
- Look.
I may not know much.
but I do know this:
Europeans love
Americans.
Really?
More than half
are women.
Okay. Sure.
But... I really like MJ.
man. okay?
She's awesome. she's super funny
in a kind of dark way.
Sometimes I catch her
looking at me.
I feel like
I've stood up...
- She's coming.
- What up. dorks?
Excited about
the science trip?
Hey. yeah. We're just
talking about the trip.
Yeah.
and Peter's plan.
You have a plan?
I don't...
I don't have a plan.
He's... He's just gonna
collect tiny spoons
when we're traveling
to other countries.
Like a...
Like a grandmother?
I'm not collecting
tiny spoons.
He's collecting
Oh. okay. well...
that was a real
roller coaster.
- [CHUCKLES]
- By the way. travel tip:
You should download a VPN
on your phone.
so the government can't
track you while abroad.
Smart... Will do.
- [BELL RINGS]
- [SIGHS]
Dude. I think
that went really great.
MAY: When I Blipped
back to my apartment.
the family that was living there
was very confused.
The wife thought
that I was a mistress.
The grandma thought
that I was a ghost.
- [CROWD CHUCKLES]
- It was... It was really a mess.
Thank you all for coming out
to support those who have been
displaced by the Blip.
And. of course.
thanks to our very own
Spider-Man!
[CHEERING AND APPLAUDING]
- [CLEARS THROAT]
- [FEEDBACK SQUEALS]
Thank you. Miss Parker.
for having me.
And thank you. you guys.
And thank you.
Spider-Man.
He'll be right back out
to take photos and videos.
Thank you!
[CHEERING AND APPLAUDING]
- That was amazing.
- That was great.
That was so cool.
I was so nervous.
I was a little stiff.
I wasn't in the pocket.
- No. I thought you did great.
- You were a little stiff.
Uh. yeah. I felt that too.
I felt that too.
- It's fine. fine.
- Okay.
- Did you get your passport?
- Yeah.
- Mini toothpaste?
- Yeah. I did.
[DOOR CREAKS]
Hey. sorry I'm late.
Happy. Hey.
Oh. you look lovely.
- Thanks. You too.
- Thank you.
- New dress?
- Yeah. yes. it is.
It's a new beard.
It's my... My Blip beard.
'Cause I grew it
in the Blip.
It's a Blip beard.
I see. Yeah.
The reason I'm late is
because this was misplaced.
Can you believe it?
It's enormous.
Not the amount.
the size.
The amount's nice too.
They're generous.
Pepper Potts said. sorry
she couldn't be here.
I think I'm gonna go change
the Sterno
under the vegan lasagna.
Spider-Man. go shake hands.
Will do.
What just happened?
Heads up.
Nick Fury's calling you.
- Nick Fury's gonna call me? Why?
- Yeah.
Why? He probably has hero stuff
for you to do.
You're a superhero.
He calls superheroes.
If it was that important.
he'd probably call
someone else. not me.
- [PHONE BUZZING]
- Apparently not.
No caller ID.
That's him.
I don't wanna
talk to Fury.
- Answer the phone.
- Why?
If you don't talk to him.
I have to and I don't want to.
- Why not?
- I'm scared. Answer the phone.
- You sent Fury to voicemail?
- Yeah.
You don't send Fury
to voicemail.
They're calling me.
- I gotta go.
- You gotta talk to him.
I'm gonna call him. I promise.
I'm gonna call him. I will.
You do not ghost
Nick Fury.
I promise you. I'll call him.
After my trip.
Hey!
- [AUDIENCE CHEERING]
- [PHONE RINGS]
Yeah. hi.
No. no. he's not ghosting you.
- [CLAMORING]
- [CAMERA SHUTTERS CLICKING]
Okay. one question at a time.
Are you
the head Avenger?
the head Avenger now?
Uh. no. I'm not.
If aliens come back.
what are you gonna do?
what will you do?
Does anyone have
neighborhood questions?
Sean Winford.
Queens Tribune.
What's it like to take over
from Tony Stark?
Those are
big shoes to fill.
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
I'mma...
I'm gonna go.
Thanks. everyone. for coming.
[CLAMORING]
[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTS]
[SIGHS]
[PHONE BUZZING]
[BUZZING]
[♪♪♪]
[SIGHS]
[SNIFFS]
Okay.
[♪♪♪]
Hungry?
[LAUGHING]
So sorry.
I thought you could sense that
with your Peter-tingle.
Please do not start calling it
my Peter-tingle.
So. what's up? You can dodge
bullets but not bananas?
No. I just really
need this vacation.
I need a break.
You deserve it. Mm.
Yeah.
You know what?
You should pack your suit.
just in case.
I have a tingle about it.
Please stop saying
"tingle." May.
No.
[♪♪♪]
No. No. I'm not.
Vacation. yeah!
MAN: Can you help
me get my stuff up?
- WOMAN: Oh. sorry. that's mine.
- MAN: No worries.
CHILD:
Give me a tablet.
Do you want first shift
or second?
I could take either.
Give me the third shift.
I took an Ambien.
I can't chaperone
kids alone.
Yo. Parker.
This is called
an airplane.
It's like buses
you're used to.
except it flies over
poor neighborhoods
instead of driving
through them.
- Ma'am?
- Hmm?
He Blipped. so technically.
he's 16. not 21.
I'll take that.
She's lying.
I don't even know this girl.
Classic MJ. right?
Did you know Brad
was coming?
It... It's so weird.
Like. one day.
he's that kid who cried
and got nosebleeds
all the time.
and suddenly. we Blip back.
and he's totally ripped
and super nice
and all these girls
are after him.
Not all the girls
No. man.
they're all after him.
- [LAUGHING] Yeah.
- Here.
Anyway. on to more important
things. It's a nine-hour flight.
We can play Beast Slayers
the whole time.
WOMAN:
Are you excited?
I need help
to sit next to MJ.
[SIGHS]
Seriously?
Yes. seriously.
What about our plan?
American bachelors
in Europe.
That's your plan.
That's a solo plan.
Come on. this is my plan.
Please.
[SIGHS]
[♪♪♪]
Uh. hey. guys.
Uh. there's an old lady
sitting in front of us
wearing a crazy amount
of perfume.
and it's kind of setting off
Peter's allergies.
Um. you know. Betty.
if you could just
switch seats with him.
that would be...
He's allergic
to perfume?
Yeah. yeah.
because. um. it...
It makes his eyes water.
- and he can't really...
- Peter has a perfume allergy?
Oh. uh...
From experience.
allergies are no joke.
I can feel hives
breaking out already.
MJ. stand up.
Ned. take MJ's spot.
MJ. you take my spot.
Peter.
let's get you out of there.
- MJ: Sorry.
- HARRINGTON: Zach. Sebastian.
you take Ned and Peter's seats.
Ned. thanks for bringing this
to my attention.
Your safety is my
responsibility.
- And Mr. Dell's. but he's...
- [SNORING]
I got it for now.
Let's go. Peter!
Let's go!
Yeah. I have a small bladder.
so I took the aisle.
So did you wanna
play Beast Slayer?
Nope.
Have you ever played
any kind of PC game or...?
- No.
- Got it. Ahem.
Did I tell you my wife
pretended to Blip out?
Turns out. she ran off
with a guy in her hiking group.
We had a fake funeral
for her...
Well. the funeral
was real
because I thought
she was dead.
Do you wanna
see the video?
Oh. I got
a dual headphone adapter
if you wanna
watch a movie.
Only if it's depressing.
Or hilarious.
Oh. you have
a dual headphone adapter.
We can watch together.
CAPTAIN:
Good afternoon.
this is your captain speaking.
Our flight time today will
be eight hours.
49 minutes
to Venice. Italy.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
[♪♪♪]
[WOMAN SINGING IN ITALIAN]
Oh! Oh!
[DINGS]
[SNORING]
Hey man. did you see Brad and MJ
on the plane?
They were watching movies
and laughing the entire time.
Dude. don't worry.
okay?
I'm sure
that's nothing.
Hey. babe.
Can you hold this for me?
- Yeah. of course.
- Thanks.
[SIGHS]
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
What was that?
Uh. well.
we got to talking on the plane.
and it turns out.
we have a lot in common.
So. uh. we're boyfriend
and girlfriend now.
Whatever happened to being
an American bachelor in Europe?
Peter. those were the words
of a boy.
And that boy met a woman.
A very strong
and powerful woman.
And now.
that boy's a man.
- BETTY: Babe?
- Coming. babe.
- [BEEPING]
- [MAN SPEAKS IN ITALIAN]
[WHINES]
There's nothing in there.
I swear.
[♪♪♪]
These. no.
[WOMAN SINGING IN ITALIAN]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY]
PETER:
Sorry. Sorry.
- I'm here.
- HARRINGTON: Wait. wait. wait.
- PETER: I'm here.
- HARRINGTON: Thank goodness.
[ALL WHOOPING]
[CHEERING]
HARRINGTON:
Looks like we're here.
They're doing renovations
to the place.
- Getting some upgrades.
- JOSH: Oh. this is trash.
- That must be the concierge.
- Okay.
BOY:
Come on. man.
HARRINGTON:
Everyone. here we are.
- [MEOWING]
- Whoa!
- BOY: Wow!
- DELL: Come on in.
This place
is sinking.
- You mean. "charming."
- BETTY: It stinks.
Okay. everybody.
drop your bags off.
We're gonna meet at the
da Vinci Museum at 3. Let's go!
- !Vámanos!
- MJ: It's "andiamo."
Andiamo!
When in Rome.
do as Romans do.
When you're in Venice.
your socks get wet.
[WOMAN SINGING
IN ITALIAN]
What's up. Flash Mob?
How you guys doing?
I'm here in
St. Marco Polo's...
[GROANS]
- This is so much fun.
- Yeah?
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
[BEEPING]
[SHUTTER CLICKS]
Oh!
Three. two. one...
say pizza!
ALL: Pizza! Pizza time!
[PIGEONS COOING]
- Buongiorno.
- MAN: Buongiorno.
Hi. Uh...
I'm looking for a. uh...
[SPEAKS ITALIAN]
[♪♪♪]
It's perfect.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY]
[SPEAKS ITALIAN]
- What?
- [MJ SPEAKS ITALIAN]
The most perfect word.
Italians created it.
I discovered it.
- What does it mean?
- It means a million things.
I don't know.
Get out of my face.
I don't know
and get out of my face.
It's the best thing Italy
created. except for espresso.
Oh. so you've been
drinking espresso?
Hey. German?
American.
- A rose for you.
- [SPEAKS ITALIAN]
Whoa.
"Boh" is my
new superpower.
It's like the anti-"aloha."
I was born to say this word.
So. what's in the bag?
Oh. uh...
[SPEAKS ITALIAN]
Nice.
[WATER GURGLING]
[GROWLING]
MJ:
Whoa. cool.
[SEAGULLS SQUAWKING]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY]
[GURGLING]
[♪♪♪]
What was that?
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[BOTH SCREAMING]
- Betty! You okay?
- Yeah.
- MAN: Oh. my God!
- Come on.
BETTY:
Guys. we gotta go!
[GROANS]
- What is that?
- I don't know.
- What'll you do?
- My suit's in the hotel.
- Why?
- I'm on vacation. Ned!
Everyone will see my face.
Get them out.
Go! Just go!
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[ROARS]
Get out of here. Go!
Oh. my God.
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
Come on.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[GRUNTS]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
Oh. no. you don't.
You okay?
Get out of here. Go!
[GRUNTS]
[SPITS AND PANTS]
[ROARS]
[RUMBLING]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[PANTING]
[GRUNTING]
[GRUNTS]
[ROARS]
[GRUNTING]
PETER:
Excuse me. sir!
I... I can help.
Let me help.
I'm really strong.
and I'm sticky.
I need to lead it away
from the canals.
The da Vinci Museum.
This is why
we're here in Venice.
Oh. this is it.
It's closed.
What do you mean?
Till when?
November.
You didn't check
the website?
Oh. that's
a good idea.
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[MASK JINGLES]
Oh. come on.
DELL: Stay low. kids.
We'll be safe here.
[♪♪♪]
[PANTING]
[ROARING]
[GRUNTS]
- [YELLS]
- [BELL RINGS]
[GROANS]
[GRUNTING]
- [BELL RINGS]
- [GROANS]
[ROARS]
[GRUNTING]
[GRUNTS]
[YELLS]
- Who is that guy?
- I don't know.
but he's kicking
that water's ass.
[ROARS]
[YELLS]
[YELLING]
[PEOPLE CHEERING]
[♪♪♪]
Yeah! Yeah!
[REPORTER SPEAKING
IN ITALIAN ON TV]
It's aliens.
It has to be.
BuzzFeed says there's a sailor.
Morris Bench.
who was exposed
to an experimental
underwater generator
and got hydro powers.
You should
definitely believe
everything
on the Internet.
- Spider-Man could take him.
- What do you think it is?
[REPORTER SPEAKING
IN ITALIAN]
You know.
being a man of science...
witches.
No. no. no.
We wanna stay.
Good thing
I packed your suit. huh?
I can't believe you forgot it.
Yeah.
Who was that guy
you were with?
Was that Mr. Strange?
Doctor Strange. May.
Doctor Strange.
And. no. I don't know
who that was.
It was a new guy.
- I was trying to help him...
- That's my lunch.
Don't eat
that one.
Happy's there?
Yeah. it's Happy.
He's here.
He came by to volunteer.
And he's hanging
around the office.
- And he wants to say hi.
- I don't want... Hi. Peter.
Hey. Happy.
Sorry. I'm working hard here.
I gotta do a... A leaflet drop.
- What are you...?
- Glad you're having a good time.
Don't worry. I'm taking
care of your aunt.
So how's
the plan going?
There's been setbacks.
for sure.
Trust your instincts.
you'll be fine.
I know. Love you.
Bye.
[REPORTER SPEAKING
IN ITALIAN]
Who is that guy?
He's Iron Man and Thor
rolled into one.
[SCOFFS] He's all right.
He's no Spider-Man.
What is it with you
and Spider-Man?
What?
He's just awesome. okay?
He protects the neighborhood
and. you know. he's inspiring.
He inspires me
to be a better man.
What's up. dickwad?
Thought you drowned.
[SPEAKING IN ITALIAN]
Sounds like
his name's Mysterio.
"L'uomo del misterio"
is Italian
for "man of mystery."
They don't know
who he is.
Mysterio.
BOTH:
Cool name.
Babe.
So how much of that
did you actually see?
Not much. I was running.
Right. Me too.
I was also running...
away.
So Paris tomorrow.
Go to the Eiffel Tower.
Should be great.
Yeah. I read it was secretly
built as a mind control antenna
to create an army
of the insane.
Oh.
It's my favorite
destination on the trip.
[CHUCKLES]
What are you gonna do about
the water monster?
Nothing. It's dead.
Besides. that Mysterio guy's
all over it.
Look. I just wanna
spend time with MJ.
We were talking about Paris.
and I think she really likes me.
That's nice.
Reminds me of when
Betty and I fell in love.
I had just finished
my fruit cobbler. and...
You're a very difficult person
to contact. Spider-Man.
You're Nick Fury.
And you just shot Ned.
FURY:
It's a mild tranquilizer.
He'll be all right.
So good to finally meet you.
I saw you at the funeral.
I didn't think that was
a good time to exchange numbers.
No. that would've
been inappropriate.
- That's what I just said.
- Right.
The important thing is.
you're here.
I tried to bring you here.
You avoided me.
and now you're here.
What a coincidence.
Wait. Was this
a coincidence?
I used to know everything.
Then I come back
five years later.
and now I know nothing.
No intel. no team.
And a high school kid
is dodging my calls.
Here's what I do know:
[POWERS UP]
A week ago. a village in Mexico
was wiped out by a cyclone.
Witnesses say
that cyclone had a face.
[NED SNORING]
Three days later.
a similar event in Morocco.
- A village was...
- [KNOCKING]
Just making the rounds.
See if anyone needs
any counseling
after today's
traumatic events.
No. we'll be okay.
We're fine. Thank you.
Great because I'm...
I'm not qualified to actually...
Oh. he's passed out.
I'm not qualified to
do it anyway. so good night.
That was my teacher.
Sorry about that.
You were saying?
A village was
destroyed by what
may well be
another world-threatening...
BETTY:
Babe. you still awake?
You're not answering
any of my texts.
Um. he's asleep. Betty.
BETTY:
Oh. already?
- Mm-hmm. Yeah.
- BETTY: Okay.
That's why
it's imperative...
DELL: Hey. boys.
So that canal water today
was filled
with dangerous bacteria...
Another person
touches that door.
we are going
to attend another funeral.
- Suit up.
- DELL: Let me know if
either of you
develop vomiting.
[♪♪♪]
Stark left these for you.
Really?
"Uneasy lies the head
that wears the crown."
Stark said
you wouldn't get that
because it's not
a Star Wars reference.
[SCOFFS]
You can lose the mask.
Everyone here
has seen you without it.
You'd only be
feigning anonymity
and breathing through spandex
for no good reason.
[GRUNTS]
Come on.
Yeah.
Over there.
we have Maria Hill.
- That is Dimitri.
- [GUN COCKS]
And this is Mr. Beck.
Mysterio?
What?
Doesn't matter.
It's what my friends
have been calling you.
Well. you can
call me Quentin.
You handled yourself well
out there today.
I saw what you did
with the tower.
We could use someone like you
on my world.
Thanks.
I'm sorry. Your world?
Mr. Beck is from Earth.
Just not yours.
BECK:
There are multiple realities.
This is Earth Dimension 616.
I'm from Earth 833.
I'm sorry. you're saying
there's a multiverse?
'Cause I thought
that was theoretical.
That changes how we understand
the initial singularity.
We're talking about
an eternal inflation system.
How does that even work
with all the quantum...?
It's insane.
S-sorry. It's really cool.
Don't ever apologize for being
the smartest one in the room.
- [SCOFFS]
- Anyway...
[♪♪♪]
They were born in stable orbits
within black holes.
Creatures formed
from the primary elements:
Air. water. fire. earth.
The Science Division had
a technical name.
We just called them
Elementals.
Versions of them exist
across our mythologies.
Turns out.
the myths are real.
Like Thor.
Thor was a myth. now I study him
in my physics class.
These myths are threats.
They first materialized
on my Earth many years ago.
We mobilized
and fought them.
but with each battle.
they grew. got stronger.
I was part of the last battalion
left trying to stop them.
All we did was
delay the inevitable.
The Elementals are here now.
attacking the same coordinates.
Our satellites
confirm it.
So thank Mr. Beck for destroying
the other three.
There's only one left:
fire.
The strongest
of them all.
The one that destroyed
my Earth.
It's the one
that took my family.
[♪♪♪]
I'm sorry.
And it will be in Prague
in approximately 48 hours.
We have one mission:
kill it.
And you're coming with us.
I'm sorry.
did you say Prague? Heh.
Mr. Fury.
this all seems like bigtime.
you know. huge superhero
kind of stuff.
And. I mean. I'm just a friendly
neighborhood Spider-Man. sir.
Bitch. please.
You've been to space.
I know.
but that was an accident.
There's gotta be someone else
you can use.
- What about Thor?
- Off-world.
Okay. um. Doctor Strange.
- Unavailable.
- Captain Marvel.
Don't invoke her name.
Sir. look.
I really wanna help. I do.
If my aunt finds out I left
my class trip. she'll kill me.
If I'm seen in Europe
after the Washington Monument.
my class will figure out
who I am. and then...
Then the whole world
will figure out
who I am.
then I'm done.
Okay.
I understand.
I'm sorry. what?
Why don't you get back
before your teachers miss you
and become suspicious.
Dimitri.
Take him back to the hotel.
please.
Yes.
Thank you. Mr. Fury.
And. uh. good luck.
[♪♪♪]
See you. kid.
Yeah. see you.
- Bye. ma'am.
- MARIA: Yeah.
Okay. drink lots
of water.
I'm gonna get you
a vitamin C pill.
- You cannot get sick. okay?
- Okay. Thanks. baby.
Hey. man. are you sure
you're good?
Oh. dude. I'm fine.
- Okay. Nice.
- Don't worry.
Seriously. getting tranq'd
in the neck by Nick Fury.
probably the coolest thing
to ever happen to me.
- It is pretty awesome.
- Yeah.
I'm happy I don't have
to go to Prague.
- Seriously.
- Good news.
We're going to Prague. Huh?
- What?
- Prague?
Yeah. Tour company called.
They upgraded us.
You should've heard me
on the phone with them.
I really gave them hell.
All I heard was
crying.
Look at
our upgraded ride. Huh?
Whoa. bro.
you see that?
It's pretty sick.
I'm impressed.
Mr. Harrington.
Oh. come on.
Peter. what...?
What's going on?
I think Nick Fury just hijacked
our summer vacation.
I'm. uh. Mr. Harrington
to the kids...
- BOY: Oh. all right.
- Okay.
Awesome.
Yeah. Awesome.
[♪♪♪]
[WOMAN SINGING
IN SLOVAK]
Yo. what's up. Flash Mob?
It's your boy. the Big F.
cruising through the Alps
with my private driver. Dimitri.
[♪♪♪]
"For the next Tony Stark.
I trust you.
Say EDITH."
EDITH: Stand by for
retinal and biometric scan.
Retinal and biometric scan
accepted.
- Hello?
- EDITH: Hello. Peter.
I am EDITH. Tony Stark's
augmented-reality
security and defense system.
- So he made you for me?
- EDITH: No. But you have access
- to all of Tony's protocols.
- Cool.
EDITH: Would you like
to see what I can do?
[♪♪♪]
EDITH stands for
"Even dead. I'm the hero."
Tony loved his acronyms.
- [CHUCKLES] Yeah. he did.
- EDITH: I have access to
the entire
Stark Global Security network.
including multiple
defense satellites.
as well as back doors
to all major
telecommunication networks.
Whoa.
Is MJ texting?
No. Don't look at it.
Don't look at it.
That's wrong. That's wrong.
[PHONES CHIME]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY]
Petrol and toilets.
Ten minutes!
Flash Mob. this is what
we doing out here...
Toilet. toilet. toilet.
Which way to the toilet?
Ten minutes.
everyone.
Dimitri.
where exactly are we?
Okay.
I'll figure it out.
Oh. my gosh.
it's so sick.
It's beautiful.
What?
[♪♪♪]
Hello.
Close the door.
Um...
I'm Peter Parker.
Take off your clothes.
- Excuse me?
- You told Fury
Spider-Man
cannot be seen in Europe.
So I made you this.
another suit.
Oh. uh. thank you.
I'm sure it fits fine.
I don't need to try...
- Take off your clothes.
- Okay.
Sure.
- It's a little embarrassing.
- Now. Hurry up.
This is weird. Heh.
No. no. no. Don't...
Whoa.
Uh...
Sorry. I thought
this was the bathroom.
This is not
what it looks like.
- Just...
- Yeah.
- What are you doing?
- I'll leave you alone.
Oh. my God.
Don't shoot anybody.
Brad? It's not what
it looks like. buddy.
- Hey. man. look. that's...
- Look. Peter.
I'm not here to judge
your life choices. dude.
If you want to hook up with
some random European chick.
- that's on you.
- That's not what that was.
I can't pretend
I didn't see what I saw.
I know you're trying
to get with MJ. It's obvious.
- But I like her too.
- Wait a minute. Hey. hey.
You cannot show her
that photo. dude.
I'm sorry. man.
I have to.
She deserves the truth.
Okay. put your one foot
in front of the other.
and. everybody.
back on the bus.
HARRINGTON: It's been 10 minutes.
Let's go!
[STUDENTS CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY]
FLASH: What's up. Flash Mob?
It's your boy. Big F...
- EDITH?
- EDITH: Hello. Peter.
- How can I help you?
- Hey. There's this guy
in my class who's gonna
ruin everything...
EDITH: Peter.
I'm having difficulty hearing you.
Can you please speak up?
Um. Brad Davis.
He has a photo of me.
EDITH:
Brad Davis. Is he a target?
Is Brad a target? Um...
Yeah. He's a target.
He's a target.
EDITH:
Copy that.
Target is Brad Davis.
Initiating strike.
Initiating what. now?
EDITH:
Intercept point determined.
- Releasing kill vehicle.
- EDITH.
[♪♪♪]
- Oh. my God.
- Dope glasses. Parker.
- How'd you pay for these?
- Flash. give them back.
- I'm paying you a compliment.
- Please give me...
I'm so sorry.
EDITH. don't kill Brad.
EDITH:
Do you want me to cancel
the drone strike
on Brad Davis?
- Did you just punch Flash?
- No.
EDITH:
Firing.
Oh. look out!
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[STUDENTS EXCLAIMING]
Hey. this is not the autobahn!
- EDITH.
- DELL: Harrington!
- Is this the autobahn?
- HARRINGTON: Appears to be.
EDITH:
Commencing second strike.
Peter. Plant your fanny
and buckle up.
Look at
the baby mountain goats!
- Baby mountain goats?
- DELL: Ooh. I see them.
[♪♪♪]
I don't see
any mountain goats.
[PANTING]
You missed them.
I know you think none of us
have noticed. Peter...
What?
...but your new look.
I love it.
- Right. babe?
- Thanks.
NED: Yeah. Sophisticated.
classy. very European.
Oh. man.
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
Let's try that again.
BRAD: Uh. this is so weird.
It was right here on my phone.
- I-I...
- Yeah. Weird.
[SIGHS]
Ow.
[MAN SINGING IN CZECH]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY]
[PIANO PLAYING]
- BOY: Whoa. freaking beautiful.
- GIRL: This is amazing.
Wow. this place
is so classy.
Yeah. so why
are we here?
Speak for yourself.
[CHUCKLES]
I'm home.
What can I say?
The squeaky wheel gets
the upgrade grease.
Everyone get settled in. rest up
because tonight. big surprise.
- is Prague's annual...
- [PHONE BUZZES]
- ...Carnival of Lights.
- BOY: Yeah!
- Hello?
- MARIA: Parker. it's Hill.
There's an earpiece
with your suit.
Put it on and await
further instructions.
- Understood?
- Uh. yes. ma'am.
- MARIA: Yeah.
- Hey. man.
- Hey.
- Look. I am so sorry
if I seem like I'm preoccupied
with my relationship.
I'm still your guy
in the chair.
No. it's all good.
Don't worry about it.
- Okay. Great. great.
- It's fine.
So. what's the status
on the Elemental thing?
- Where's it gonna happen?
- Uh. here in the city.
- Peter. we're here.
- I know. I know. It's not good.
It's... I'm figuring it out.
You have to do something.
Peter. please.
We're all counting on you.
- Ned.
- Yeah. Yeah. babe.
HARRINGTON: The good news is.
we've all got our own rooms.
- BOY: It's about time.
- GIRL: Serious?
- FURY: Parker? Parker!
- Yes. sir.
That thing is going to be here
in a few hours.
- Are we boring you?
- He's not bored.
He's thinking about
how you kidnapped him.
He had obstacles.
I removed them.
They still won't
evacuate the city.
[SIGHS]
Idiots.
So. what's the plan.
Parker?
I will be in
the cathedral tower.
keeping watch
for the fire monster.
When that shows up.
I will radio you guys.
- and then Mr. Beck and I will...
- My name is Mysterio.
[CHUCKLES]
That's when Mysterio and I
will move in.
BECK:
Peter. listen to me.
The best hope you have.
the only hope.
is to stop it here now.
no matter what the cost.
Maneuver it away
from civilians if you can.
but most important.
keep it away from metal.
If it gets too big.
it'll be able to
draw power
from the Earth's core.
After that.
there's no way to stop it.
Hey. my friends are here.
I can't help but think
we're putting them in danger.
You're worried about us
hurting your friends?
You. who called a drone strike
on your own school tour bus?
Stark gave you
a multibillion-dollar
A.R. tactical
intelligence system.
and the first thing
you do with it
is try and blow up
your friends.
It's clear to me that
you were not ready for this.
[♪♪♪]
Fury asked me to come up here
and see how you were doing.
He just... He felt bad
about snapping at you.
Really?
You guys do have sarcasm
on this Earth. right?
[CHUCKLES]
How you feeling?
Uh...
I didn't think I was gonna have
to save the world this summer.
I know that makes me sound
like such a jerk. I just...
I had this plan with this girl
that I really like...
and now it's all ruined.
You're not a jerk
for wanting a normal life. kid.
It's a hard path.
You see things.
You do things.
You make choices.
People look up to you...
and even if you win a battle.
sometimes they die.
I like you. Peter.
You're a good kid.
There's a part of me that
wants me to tell you. just...
turn around.
run away from all this.
Then there's
another part of me
that knows what
we're about to fight.
what's at stake.
and I'm glad you're here.
Me too.
But you're worried about
your friends.
Yeah.
Just always feel like
I'm putting them in danger.
Look.
just get them inside
and keep them in a safe place
for just a few hours.
They'll be all right.
It's really nice to have
somebody to talk to
about superhero stuff.
you know?
Anytime.
And. hey.
we survive this.
you'll have all summer
to kill Brad.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
See you out there.
All right.
[♪♪♪]
Scusi.
Sorry. that's Italian.
[MUTTERS]
Okay. EDITH?
Oh. come on.
- EDITH: Hello. Peter.
- Hey. uh...
I need a way to keep my friends
inside the next few hours.
EDITH:
Let's see what we can do.
Good news.
We're going to the opera!
- You're kidding me.
- The opera?
Don't look at me.
What happened
to the carnival?
This is upgrade living. guys.
Come on. The tour company
just gave us these tickets.
For free! Do you have any idea
how much opera tickets cost?
No. because none of us have ever
wanted to go to the opera. ever.
Uh. I think this is gonna be
culturally enriching for us.
Thank you. Ned.
Everyone.
this is gonna be. maybe.
the best four hours
of our whole trip.
ALL:
Four hours?
Guys. I think this
is gonna be fun. Seriously.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY]
I bet now you're all happy
I had you pack a nice outfit.
Yeah. because we'd much
rather go to a four-hour opera
instead of the biggest party
in the world.
Again.
don't look at me.
MARIA [ON COMM]:
Parker. do you copy?
Comm check. one. two.
HARRINGTON:
Okay. here we are.
Beat the rush.
Yeah. the rush out.
Lucky for us. we got
the best seats in the house.
DELL:
Let's go.
Hey.
I'll save you a seat.
[ORCHESTRA TUNING]
You look really pretty.
And therefore.
I have value?
No. No. that's not what
I meant at all. I was just...
I'm messing with you.
[CHUCKLES]
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- You look pretty too.
- Thank you.
- Oh. my gosh! Opera glasses!
- So cute.
- Can I...?
- Yeah.
Want to go in on a pair?
You mean.
sit next to each other?
Yeah.
FURY [ON COMM]:
Are you in position?
- No.
- Okay. No...
FURY:
Why the hell not? Parker?
You don't want to
sit next to me.
or. no. you just
don't want the glasses?
I didn't mean that.
Uh. uh...
If you go ahead.
I'll go grab us a pair.
I'll save you
a seat next to me.
Awesome.
A lot of seats.
so I'll be up there.
Okay.
- FURY: Parker.
- No. I'm coming. I'm...
Hey. I gotta go.
Could you tell MJ
that I'm sick
or something?
Okay. Be careful.
And Peter.
whatever you do.
please steer the monster away
from the opera house.
Yeah. Ned. I know.
- Okay.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
- Gotta go.
[ORCHESTRA STARTS PLAYING]
[SIGHS]
[ORCHESTRA MUSIC SWELLS]
FURY: Parker!
You better be on your way.
Coming.
[MAN SINGING ARIA IN CZECH]
Where do you think she's going?
To the carnival?
- Oh. I... I don't...
- We should go. Yes. we should go.
Come on. let's go.
Come on.
[SIGHS]
[LIVELY MUSIC PLAYING]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING. CHEERING]
[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTS]
All right. I'm in position.
Uh. as soon as
I see something.
Beck. I'll. uh...
I'll let you know.
- BECK: Roger that.
- FURY: How's the suit?
Ah. the suit's great.
It's awesome.
It's a little tight
around the old web-shooter.
- FURY: Parker!
- Okay. I'll shut up.
Oh. my God. babe.
isn't this beautiful?
Yeah. it's real beautiful.
babe.
- What's wrong?
- You know. honestly. I just...
I don't do well with big crowds.
so maybe we should...
I have the perfect thing.
Come on.
Heh.
[CAROUSEL MUSIC PLAYING]
Don't worry. babe.
We'll get away from the crowds.
get some fresh air.
You'll feel
a thousand times better.
[WATER BUBBLING]
Energy spiking.
We have seismic activity.
[RUMBLING]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[ROARING]
Okay. he's here! Beck. are you
ready? You know what to do.
BECK:
On your lead. Spider-Man.
BETTY:
No. come back!
Come back and help us!
You're up. kid.
[GRUNTS]
[ROARING]
- Wait. wait. Is that...?
- [GASPS]
Do you think
that's Spider-Man?
Uh-uh.
No. no. no.
It's a European
rip-off version of him.
I actually read about him.
It's not him.
[CAROUSEL MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTING]
No. Beck!
He's got the carousel!
He's getting bigger!
What's his name?
Uh. it's Night...
Night Monkey.
- Night Monkey?
- Yeah.
- Night Monkey!
- Yeah. Night Monkey.
- Night Monkey. help!
- Save us!
- What?
BETTY:
Night Monkey. we're stuck!
- Oh. no. no.
- BETTY: Help us! Help!
[ROARING]
[GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
[GASPING]
PETER:
Are you okay?
On to Plan B?
Yeah! We gotta hit him
with something he can't absorb!
I go left.
you go right! Now!
[♪♪♪]
[ROARS]
[GRUNTING]
Okay. shoot him!
Yeah!
[GROANS]
That hurt him.
Keep it coming.
[GRUNTS]
BECK: Spider-Man.
keep your distance.
PETER:
I'm trying!
BECK: Can't let him get
near the Ferris wheel.
PETER:
Okay. I'm on it!
[GRUNTING]
[ROARS]
[BOTH SCREAM]
- [SCREAMING]
- Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
PETER:
Whoa. what is that?!
- Betty! Betty!
- [SCREAMING]
- [TIRES SCREECH]
- [ENGINE REVS]
[GASPS]
PETER: That's it! Nice!
Nice! You got him!
[ROARS]
No. no. no.
It's too late.
Whatever happens...
I'm glad we met.
Beck.
what are you doing?
What I should have done
last time.
[GROANING]
Beck. don't do it!
[GRUNTS]
Beck!
[♪♪♪]
Mr. Beck?
[PANTING]
Oh. thank God.
[GRUNTS]
[PANTING]
I would totally kiss you.
but I think I just threw up
in my mouth a little.
[STAMMERS]
I might have a mint.
So it's over?
That was the last of them.
But not the last threat
we'll ever face.
We need to stay vigilant.
There's a void in this world
for someone like you.
Hill and I are going to Europol
headquarters in Berlin tomorrow.
You should join us.
Thank you. I just might
take you up on that.
[SIGHS] You got gifts. Parker.
but you didn't wanna be here.
Mr. Fury. I...
I'd love to have you
in Berlin too.
But you got to decide whether
you're going to step up or not.
Stark chose you.
He made you an Avenger.
I need that.
The world needs that.
Maybe Stark was wrong.
Was he?
The choice is yours.
[♪♪♪]
Let's get a drink.
I'm not 21.
- [PEOPLE CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
- [MUSIC PLAYING SOFTLY]
Hey.
You gotta celebrate.
We did something good tonight.
Yeah.
Fury was right.
Tony did a lot
for me...
so I owe it to him.
to everybody.
Do you?
Yeah. I mean...
Mr. Stark gave me
the chance to be more.
He wanted me to be
better than him.
And Fury just wants me
to live up to that.
What do you want. Peter?
- What do you mean?
- What do you want?
[SCOFFS]
I don't know.
What do you want?
Peter Parker. Now.
I know you're
thinking about it.
I wanna go on my trip.
right?
I want to go back on my trip
with my friends.
And go to
the top of the Eiffel Tower
with the girl who I really like
and tell her how I feel...
- and give her a kiss.
- Whoa.
- [CHUCKLES] Shut up. man.
- [LAUGHS]
You're not gonna do that.
are you?
- No. I can't.
- Why not?
Because I have too much
of a responsibility.
[SPEAKS IN CZECH]
- Oh. my God. Thank you so much.
- What are those?
- Are those the...?
- EDITH glasses. yeah.
They were just
on the floor?
Try them on.
Let's see how they look.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I actually
really like them.
Can I be
completely honest?
Please.
They look really stupid.
Oh.
But maybe they have
a contact-lens version.
You try them on.
- [CHUCKLES] No. come on.
- Try them on.
- I don't wanna try them on.
- Just put them on.
[SCOFFS]
What do you think. kid?
[SIGHS]
[♪♪♪]
[SOFTLY]
"Next Tony Stark. I trust you."
[NORMALLY] "For the next Tony
Stark. I trust you."
What?
Stark left me a message
with those glasses:
"For the next Tony Stark.
I trust you."
I'm still not following.
How many lemonades have you had?
He knew every mistake
I ever made.
He must've known I wasn't ready
for something like this.
Why would
he give it to you?
Maybe he didn't trust me
to have EDITH.
he just trusted me
to pick who should.
It makes much more sense.
He knew I'd do what's right.
He's not gonna
give them to Fury
because Fury would
give himself EDITH.
You're probably right.
Right. so the world needs
the next Iron Man.
And it's not me. I'm
a 16-year-old kid from Queens.
It needs to be an adult
with some experience
and that's good
like Tony Stark. like you.
No. Peter. come on. No.
- EDITH?
- EDITH: Hello. Peter.
Hi. Yeah. um...
I'd like to transfer your
control over to Quentin Beck.
- Peter. what are you doing?
- Doing the right thing.
EDITH: Any transfer will
require confirmation.
Stark gave you
the glasses.
Stark gave me a choice.
It's my choice to make.
I'm gonna make it.
You're a soldier. a leader.
You stopped the Elementals.
You saved my life.
You saved the world. okay?
He'd want you to have them.
EDITH:
Waiting for confirmation.
Confirm.
Welcome to the Avengers.
[♪♪♪]
They look good on you.
Thank you.
It's an honor.
Yeah.
Mr. Stark would've
really liked you.
- Where you headed?
- I'm gonna go find MJ.
Good luck. kid. I'll give you
a fifty-fifty chance.
You're pretty awkward.
[CHUCKLES]
- [CHUCKLES]
- Yeah.
- See you later. man.
- See you.
[♪♪♪]
See?
That wasn't so hard.
- Yes!
- [ALL CHEERING]
Somebody get
this stupid costume off me!
[♪♪♪]
[SIGHS]
Okay. we got EDITH. Get these
connected to our system.
ALL [CHANTING]:
Toast! Toast! Toast!
This is a big win. but we still
got a lot of work to do.
Toast! Toast! Toast!
MAN:
Yeah!
Okay. toasts!
Give me that. Doug.
To the man
who brought us all together.
our former boss.
Tony Stark.
ALL:
Boo!
The jester king.
Literally wrapped
in wealth and technology
that he was unfit to wield.
Like the holographic system
I designed.
A revolutionary breakthrough
with limitless applications
that Tony turned
into a self-therapy machine
and renamed...
Binarily Augmented
Retro-Framing. or BARF.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHING]
Oh. $611 million
for my little
therapeutic experiment.
[♪♪♪]
BECK:
He renamed my life's work...
"BARF."
I told him it was a mistake.
that my technology
could change the world.
And then...
he fired me.
Said I was...
unstable.
To Tony.
ALL:
To Tony!
Next. to William.
ALL:
William!
Tony Stark was able
to build this in a cave!
With a box of scraps!
BECK: The integration
of my illusion tech
with your weaponized drones
was brilliant.
Powerful illusions. real damage.
worked like a charm.
And it's just the beginning.
- Thank you. brother.
- To Guterman.
- WOMAN: Guterman!
- MAN: To Guterman!
The story you created
of a soldier
from another Earth
named Quentin
fighting space monsters
in Europe is totally ridiculous
and apparently the kind of thing
people will believe right now.
I mean.
everybody bought it.
- MAN 1: Gutes!
- MAN 2: Guterman!
- To Victoria.
- ALL: To Victoria!
Staging electromagnetic pulses
at each attack site
so Fury's own satellites
would confirm our lies.
Inspired idea.
- To Janice.
- ALL: Janice!
After Tony died. she was the one
who discovered that EDITH
was being handed over not to us.
not to the Defense Department.
but to a child.
- Thank you.
- MAN 3: To Janice!
And to the rest of you.
Tony Stark is gone.
There's a window of opportunity.
and someone will step up.
But these days. you can be
the smartest guy in the room.
the most qualified.
and no one cares.
Unless you're flying around
with a cape
or shooting lasers
from your hands.
no one will even listen.
Well. I've got a cape
and lasers.
[ALL CHUCKLE]
With our technology
and with EDITH.
Mysterio will be
the greatest hero on Earth!
ALL:
Yeah!
Then everyone will listen!
Not to a boozy man-child.
ALL:
No!
Not to a hormonal teenager.
ALL:
No!
To me...
and to my very wealthy crew.
To us.
ALL:
To Mysterio!
To Peter Parker.
ALL:
To Peter Parker!
Poor kid.
Let's get to work.
- Peter. oh. my God.
- Hey. Hey.
We almost died.
It's fine. It's fine.
Hey.
I'm done with the mission.
- Dude. the trip's over.
- What?
There's monsters coming out
of the ground.
Of course our parents
want us home.
Don't put me on hold.
Peter. you're not dead.
Oh. my God.
Yes. good. Stay here.
Don't... Put some clothes on.
We're booking flights.
We came for science. we're
leaving because of witches.
Welcome
to the new Dark Ages.
- What is going on?
- We're going home in the morning.
No. no. no.
All the Elementals are gone.
- Ned.
- Coming. sweetie.
Hey. can you guys keep it down?
I'm live-streaming.
- Yeah.
- Hey.
- Where were you?
Um. I got lost.
We were worried
about you.
Oh.
Good thing you're back.
Hm.
Yeah.
So much for Paris.
right?
It would've been fun.
Yeah. Night.
Night.
You look ni...
[SIGHS]
[♪♪♪]
Okay.
- Oh.
- Hey.
Hey.
Uh. look. um...
I'm not ready for this trip
to be over yet.
and I kind of want
to do something fun
that's not on the itinerary
or planned
or with Mr. Harrington.
Yes.
"Yes." like you wanna go?
Awesome. I'll see you outside
in 10 minutes.
Meet me outside
in five minutes.
- Five is good.
- Okay.
- Okay. bye.
- Bye. Heh.
[SPEAKING IN CZECH]
Night Monkey. help us!
Help! Night Monkey!
[PEOPLE CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY]
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
- Hey.
So where do
you wanna go?
- Who cares?
- Awesome.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
[♪♪♪]
[CHUCKLES]
PETER:
I'm glad we're doing this.
- MJ: Yeah. me too.
- PETER: To see the city a bit.
They used to execute people
on this bridge.
- Oh.
- They would put them in a basket.
and they would drown
in the water.
- Sorry.
- It's okay.
Uh...
There's this thing
I've been wanting
to talk to you about
for a while.
Yeah?
It's our last night
in Europe.
and I had this plan
that I wanted to tell you.
[STAMMERING]
I'm just gonna tell you.
Uh...
MJ. I...
"I'm Spider-Man."
- What?
- That's what you were gonna say.
That you're Spider-Man.
No. I'm not Spider-Man.
I mean. I've been watching you
for a while now.
It's kind of obvious.
Heh.
I'm not Spider-Man.
What would make you think
that I was Spider-Man?
- Peter. Washington?
- Yeah?
The fact that you disappear
out of nowhere for no reason.
No. I was sick. Remember?
- I had my... The tummy?
- Susan Yang thinks
- you're a male escort.
- What?
- Of course I'm not a male escort.
- Then you're Spider-Man.
- No. I'm not Spider-Man at all.
- What about tonight?
You snuck off and fought
that thing. I saw you.
You can't have seen me
because I'm not Spider-Man.
Also. on the news.
it was the Night Monkey.
- The Night Monkey?
- Yeah.
That's what it said
on the news.
and the news never lies.
Night Monkey. Okay.
What are you doing?
Well. do the Night Monkey
and Spider-Man
use the same webs?
I mean. maybe.
Maybe he's a Spider Monkey.
Who knows?
Were you only watching me
because you thought
I was Spider-Man?
Yeah.
Why else
would I be watching you?
Doesn't matter.
Just thought that maybe...
What the hell was that?
I don't know.
[♪♪♪]
What is it. some kind
of projector or something?
Yeah.
but it's really advanced.
It... It looked so real.
- It...
- Yeah. really real.
- Wait. does that mean that...?
- The Elementals are fake?
That doesn't make any sense
because we were there. right?
There was fire
and destruction. and...
Who would do something
like that?
Mysterio.
I am Spider-Man.
And I've really messed up.
Wait. You're b-being
serious right now?
- Mm-hm.
- You're 100 percent serious?
- Because it's not funny.
- No. I'm not joking.
Because I was only
like 67 percent sure.
- MJ...
- So why are you here?
Why are you
on this school trip?
I know you have a lot
of questions.
but we have to get out
of here. okay?
Okay. Okay. I can't believe
I figured it out!
[♪♪♪]
MYSTERIO:
You took everything from me!
This is for my family!
[MYSTERIO YELLING]
BECK:
Pause.
WILLIAM:
Uh... Sorry.
Yeah. can you just fast-forward
to the end?
Yep. Stand by.
All right. fly. fly. fly.
zap. zap. zap.
Pause. I'm not in love
with this choreography.
but it'll do.
Kill image.
De-cloak drones.
All right. weapons.
- You want to weaponize?
- Yep.
Weapons only. Stand by.
Nice.
Stop.
Something.
I don't know what it is.
It's something...
Just dou...
You know what?
Double the damage
and then run it again.
You want me
to double it up?
- Yeah.
- All right.
Cover your ears.
[ROARS]
Whoo! That is good!
That's good.
- We on schedule?
- Oh. yeah.
Uploading software hack
to EDITH network.
With her drones.
we'll create an event
big enough to cover
an entire city.
Well done. Make sure
every drone is weapons-hot.
We need maximum damage.
- Gonna cause a lot of casualties.
- Oh. yeah.
More casualties. more coverage.
Gotta cut through the static.
London's a beautiful city.
it'll suffer.
but they can rebuild.
If I'm the next Iron Man.
I need to save the world
from an Avengers-level threat.
But when its new savior
descends.
all those casualties
will be forgotten.
Janice. be in position
with my quick-change armor
- for the victory lap?
- Of course.
- You wanna try...?
- No. that's...
What's going on with my hand?
Why is that happening?
Oh. one of the drones
that came back from the plaza
was missing a projector.
It's fine.
Wait. and you're...?
You're telling me this now?
It's one drone. The image
will be perfect. I promise.
That projector is evidence.
It's gonna tell people
what we're doing
and how we're doing it.
I am trying to fool
7 billion people here.
including Nick Fury. who happens
to be the most paranoid
and most dangerous person
on the planet.
If he catches on
before I've killed him.
he will put a bullet
in my head.
And nobody wants a bullet
in their head. right?
Right?
William.
can you look at me?
Pull up EDITH.
EDITH:
Hello. Quentin.
Hi. honey.
I need a level-five search.
full-resource protocol
for this device.
EDITH:
Magnifying.
There.
Search everything
going in and out
of that building.
EDITH:
Located.
Shit.
You know. William.
one day.
after I've had to kill
Peter Parker because of this.
I hope you remember
that his blood is on your hands!
I can't believe
I gave Beck those glasses.
How could I be that stupid?
He's probably spying on me
right now
or sending a drone
to come and kill me.
You had access
to killer drones?
Yeah.
I didn't really want them.
especially after
I almost killed Brad.
You almost killed Brad?
Look.
I have to call Mr. Fury
and tell him
that Beck's a fraud...
- but I think he tapped my phone.
- So. what are you gonna do?
I need my suit.
and I have to go to Berlin
and talk to Mr. Fury
in person.
[PANTS]
Uh... Just...
[CLEARS THROAT]
[♪♪♪]
Oh. Ned. perfect.
The costume looks great...
for the costume party
at the prince's castle.
She knows.
I told her.
He didn't tell me.
I figured it out.
Oh.
That's cool.
Like. a long time ago.
Oh.
Look. Mysterio is a fraud.
But he saved me
and Betty's lives.
He's been faking the thing
with illusion tech.
Yeah. he's using these.
like. hologram projectors.
Whoa. That's crazy.
Yeah.
So you guys were working
the case together or what?
It's been mostly me.
Ned. call May.
get her to call Mr. Harrington.
say she wanted me to stay
with family in Berlin.
Got it. Easy.
Wow. you guys
lie with such ease.
I gotta go.
Wait. wait. wait.
The projector.
You're gonna need this.
Don't tell anyone about this.
okay?
Anyone who knows
is in danger.
[♪♪♪]
[SIGHS]
So you know too.
It's cool. I've known first.
and I've known longer.
but it's not a competition.
Heh.
[♪♪♪]
[WOMAN SPEAKING OVER PA
IN CZECH]
[PEOPLE EXCLAIMING
INDISTINCTLY]
- Excuse me. Do you know where...?
- [GASPS]
- Nacht Monkey!
- No. wait. I didn't... Oh. man.
Get in.
Mr. Fury...
You've got a lot
of explaining to do.
- No. no. no. listen.
- Wait until we're secure.
[SIGHS]
Okay.
[ALARM BEEPING]
[CLEARS THROAT]
Right.
[SEATBELT CLATTERS]
[♪♪♪]
So is there anything
you want to tell us
about your girlfriend?
He's talking about
EDITH.
I made a mistake.
I'm sorry.
but he is not
who you think he is.
Beck is a liar.
Mysterio. the Elementals.
it's all fake.
He has some illusion tech.
That's how he tricked you.
and me into giving him EDITH.
It's a projector. I pulled it
off the fire monster in Prague.
So all that death
and destruction
we witnessed
was created by this?
No. not just this.
I think he's using drones.
Well. if this is true.
then Beck's very dangerous
and we need to be smart.
Who else did you tell
about this?
Parker? Parker!
- What's wrong?
- It's Beck. He's here.
What? Hill?
No. it's just an illu...
Fury!
Unh. Aah!
[COUGHS]
- BECK: Wow. Peter. wow.
- [COUGHING]
- I thought we were close.
- [GORANING]
Fury always had to die.
but not you.
PETER:
Stop hiding. Beck!
BECK: I tried to
help you walk away.
Now you're making me
do this.
[ECHOING]
You told me.
you were just a kid.
You told me. you wanted
to run after that girl.
- MJ: Help me!
- MJ!
Oh. God!
Peter. what's going on?
I know this isn't real.
BECK:
Do you. though?
[GASPING]
MJ!
- [SCREAMING]
- MJ!
[GROANS]
I don't think you know
what's real. Peter.
[ECHOING]
Whoa! Whoa!
[YELLING]
BECK:
You need to wake up!
[GROANING]
[PANTING]
[♪♪♪]
BECK:
I mean. look at yourself.
[GRUNTING]
BECK: You are just
a scared little kid
in a sweat suit.
I created Mysterio
to give the world
someone to believe in.
I control the truth.
Mysterio is the truth.
[SCREAMS]
BECK:
If you were good enough.
maybe Tony would still
be alive.
[YELLING]
BECK: Deep down.
you know I'm right.
- [CLANGS]
- [GRUNTS]
BECK:
You made your choice.
And all you had to do
was step aside.
And now you have...
[GUNSHOT]
[GASPING]
[♪♪♪]
[SIRENS WAILING]
Fury. Unh.
Beck's people
are trying to find everyone
who could expose him.
Who'd you tell?
- Um...
- I know you told someone...
- ...so just tell me.
- Okay.
- Who did you tell?
Who else did you tell?
Just Ned and MJ
from my class.
Maybe Ned told
his girlfriend Betty.
- but that's it.
- [LAUGHING]
What?
You are so gullible.
- What?
- You're smart as a whip.
Just a...
BECK:
...sucker.
And now all your friends
have to die.
Oh. my God.
[GASPING]
It's easy to fool people
when they're already fooling
themselves.
But for what it's worth.
Peter.
I really am sorry.
[GASPS]
- EDITH.
- EDITH: Yes. Quentin.
Access files to
Peter Parker's class trip.
I need them to fly home
from London.
[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTING]
[PANTING]
[COUGHING]
[SNORING]
Hi.
Where am I?
Municipal holding
facility.
They said they found you
unconscious at the train yard.
Very dangerous.
And we gave you the shirt
because you seemed
a bit cold.
Thanks.
You guys are nice.
[CHUCKLES]
You speak really good
English.
ALL:
Welcome to the Netherlands.
I'm in the Netherlands
right now?
Yep.
Bye. Aah!
- Guard!
- The guard is on a break.
- Probably talking to his wife.
- Yeah. she's pregnant.
- Oh. yeah?
- Yeah.
[ALL SPEAKING IN DUTCH]
Yeah.
Night Monkey. Yeah.
[♪♪♪]
You guys okay?
[PANTING]
[GRUNTING]
[GROANS]
- Excuse me. sir?
- Yeah?
- Could I borrow your phone?
- Yeah.
[SPEAKS IN DUTCH]
Everyone is so nice here.
Uh...
- Okay.
- [DIALING]
Okay.
Pick up. pick up. pick up.
Hey. hey. uh...
I messed up.
I need a... I need a ride.
Where am I?
Where am I. sir?
It's Broek op Langedijk.
Hang on.
Could you say that into there?
Hi.
It's Broek op Langedijk here.
Yeah. no problem.
Heh. heh.
Thanks.
Did you get that?
Peter? Are you okay?
- Happy. is that you?
- Yeah. of course it's me.
Stop! Tell me something
only you would know.
Only I would know. Uh...
Remember we went to Germany?
You pay-per-viewed a video
in your room?
They didn't list titles.
but I could tell by the price
it was an adult film.
- And you didn't know how I knew...
- Okay. fine! It's you. Stop.
[GRUNTING]
It's so good to see you.
Peter. you'll have to tell me
what the hell is going on here.
Okay. hold still.
There we go.
Ouch.
I thought you had
super strength.
It still hurts.
- Happy. come on.
- All right. relax.
- Just a few more. There we go.
- Oh. my God.
- Relax.
- Don't tell me to relax. Happy!
How can I relax
when I messed up so bad?
I trusted Beck. Right?
I thought he was my friend.
I gave him the only thing
Mr. Stark left for me.
and now he's gonna kill
my friends and half of Europe.
so please
do not tell me to relax.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
I'm sorry. Happy. I'm sorry.
I shouldn't shout.
[SIGHS]
I just really miss him.
Yeah. I miss him too.
Everywhere I go...
I see his face.
[VOICE BREAKING] And the
whole world is asking
who's gonna be
the next Iron Man...
[SNIFFLES]
And I don't know if that's me.
Happy. I'm not Iron Man.
You're not Iron Man.
You're never gonna be
Iron Man.
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
Nobody could live up
to Tony.
Not even Tony.
Tony was my best friend.
And he was a mess.
He second-guessed
everything he did.
He was all over the place.
The one thing that he did
that he didn't second-guess
was picking you.
I don't think
Tony would have done what he did
if he didn't know that you were
gonna be here after he was gone.
Now. your friends
are in trouble.
you're all alone.
your tech is missing.
What are you gonna do
about it?
[♪♪♪]
I'm gonna kick his ass.
I mean. right now. Specifically.
what are we gonna do?
We've been hovering
over a tulip field
for the last 15 minutes.
Right.
I can't call my friends
because he's tracking
their phones.
Give me your phone.
- My cell phone?
- Yeah.
Okay. Here.
What's your password?
"Password."
No. what is your password?
- "Password." spelled out.
- Head of security.
- and your password is "password"?
- I don't feel good about it.
Hello. governor. Cup of tea?
I'm gonna be in London soon.
- They're in London.
- London. okay.
Yeah. I need a suit.
Suit?
[♪♪♪]
Okay. um...
bring up everything you have
on Spider-Man.
Yeah. open that.
Okay. no. no. no.
- What?
- Nothing.
You take care of the suit.
I'll take care of the music.
[AC/DC'S "BACK IN BLACK"
PLAYING OVER SPEAKER]
Oh. I love Led Zeppelin.
Okay. can you pull up
my web-shooters?
Isolate the Taser webs.
and reconfigure
and boost the voltage
to a factor of 25 percent.
and give me complete
manual control over detonation.
♪ Forget the hearse
'Cause I never die... ♪
I thought Kree
having sleeper cells
was top secret information.
Nick. satellites are picking up
an EM pulse.
- I thought that was over.
- It's the biggest one yet.
- Where?
- London.
Okay. the company set up
a city tour.
and then we'll grab a bite
and head to the airport.
Is no one else gonna
acknowledge how crazy this is?
Oh. yeah. I get it.
There's been nothing scientific
about this science tour
at all.
No. no. I'm talking
about Peter.
Has no one noticed
how shady he is?
I saw him in the back room
of a rest stop
with some woman
in his underwear.
and he's always
sneaking away.
like back at the opera. huh?
Now he's suddenly off the trip.
with his family in Berlin?
Is no one else here
interested in the truth?
"The very concept
of objective truth
is fading out of the world."
George Orwell.
Thank you. MJ.
Yeah. Well. since
Peter's not really here
to tell his truth.
what about you. Brad?
Why take pictures of people
in the bathroom?
Yeah. dude.
what's that about?
No. no. no.
it wasn't like that. It was...
I was trying to take a...
Let's put all
this craziness behind us
and have a nice.
peaceful afternoon.
"Sounds great. Mr. Harrington."
said the class. Okay.
I'm gonna be a cool teacher
right now.
You gotta stop doing that.
It is weird.
No more photos in the bathroom.
Urinal or stalls.
- Okay?
- HARRINGTON: Look at this.
Mr. Harrington.
this is your bus.
- We got a bus all to ourselves.
- Nice to see you all. Come along.
- I'll get this. yeah? Why not?
- Thank you.
BOY:
Yeah. Thank you. brother.
HARRINGTON:
All right.
I have the kids.
MYSTERIO:
I got here as fast as I could.
I did a full perimeter sweep.
Nothing.
Damn it.
Pulse is spiking.
I'll take
another look.
Soon as you see something.
report.
You're all we've got. Beck.
MYSTERIO: If this is what I
fear. then God help us. Fury.
God help us all.
Okay. no Avengers coming.
Good to go.
- William. launch the drones.
- Copy that. brother.
Drones are entering
the atmosphere weapons-hot.
[♪♪♪]
- Excellent. Janice?
- Working on the cape.
Get those wrinkles out.
I could be shaking hands
with the queen.
- Guterman?
- Almost in position.
- Okay. Hit it. Victoria.
- Increasing pulse.
[WHIRRING]
Whatever this is.
it's 100 times bigger
than the previous ones.
EDITH?
EDITH:
Yes. Quentin.
Show me my loose ends.
Once the show's going.
execute the kill order
on my command.
- EDITH: Copy.
- All right.
Start the show.
[THUNDER RUMBLES]
Let's save the world.
people.
I don't like this.
Something's definitely up.
You're an FOS now.
"Friend of Spider-Man."
And you have to remember.
just stay calm.
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
[CRASHING]
That doesn't
look good.
But it's fake.
nothing to worry about.
And the kids
are in the kill zone.
BECK:
Great work. Guterman.
- [CELL PHONE BUZZES]
- What?
- Happy Hogan here.
- I know. What do you want?
At Mr. Stark's.
going through his belongings.
There was a surfboard
you left behind.
- What?
- People said they didn't think
Nick Fury was a surfer. I said.
"Appearances can be deceiving."
It's not mine. And don't ever
call this number again.
[♪♪♪]
HAPPY:
Fury's got the coded message.
Your friends
are at the Tower Bridge.
Your boy called it London
Bridge. but I figured it out.
- I'll scoop them up. okay?
- Yeah.
- We're close.
- How's the suit?
- Almost done.
- Good.
- Wait. wait. whoa. whoa.
Before you go.
if something happens to me.
could you please give
this to MJ?
You'll make it back.
Give it to her yourself.
- You got this.
- I got this.
- Walk me through it.
- I know it's illusion tech.
All I do
is get inside the illusion.
then I can take it down.
find him.
and he's just a guy.
I can take EDITH
right back.
Right. but last time.
you got hit by a train.
True. but this time...
How do I explain this? Uh...
I have a sixth sense.
The Peter-tingle. That's what
you're talking about. right?
It's not working. though.
I heard it wasn't working now.
Is it?
It is working.
I don't know if it's working...
You got the Peter-tingle.
That's the plan.
I'm gonna go get
your friends.
You get that Peter-tingle
back online.
I got this. I got this.
[♪♪♪]
[WHIRRING]
Cue the lightning.
Cuing lightning.
[GASPS]
Sir. is it still safe
on the top.
or should we all come down?
Oh. my.
What did
the bus driver say?
Bus driver's gone.
- What?
- GIRL: Where?
It's okay. Mr. Dell and I
have it under control!
No. Don't drag me into this.
I'm doing my best.
Julius!
- Look...
- Oh. the witches are back.
- Oh. my God. get off the bus!
- [ALL CLAMORING]
- [HORN HONKING]
- [GASPS]
- MAN: Okay.
- Okay. follow me. kids.
[SCREAMS]
Come on. let's go!
[ROARING]
Now. that is
an Avengers-level threat.
[♪♪♪]
HARRINGTON:
This way. This way!
- Okay. Okay.
- GIRL: Oh. my God!
- MJ: Flash!
- DELL: Follow that hand.
HARRINGTON:
This way. Follow me.
- It's not real. it's not real!
- It looks real to me!
HARRINGTON:
Follow me. kids!
DELL: Earth. wind. fire. water.
Oh. no.
They joined forces
like the Power Rangers.
- You're thinking of Voltron.
- Who?
Voltron!
You're thinking of Voltron!
Hey. look.
it's Mysterio!
He's gonna save us!
[GROANING]
Wait. if Mysterio
knows we know...
- Then we're in danger.
- Yeah. and so are they.
We should go.
Kill that witch! Ba-bow!
MYSTERIO:
This is for my family!
You should get
somewhere safe. Fury.
I don't see this
ending well.
I appreciate your concern.
but I never leave my men
behind.
All right. comms check.
Can you hear me?
I can.
It's a little loud out here.
- I like the new suit.
- Thanks.
Whoa. Peter.
you sure that's not real?
Yeah. it's just 100 times bigger
than I expected.
- Still the play?
- Uh-huh.
We need to get high enough
- so Beck doesn't see me coming.
- Copy. Stay sticky.
- Hey. Happy.
- Yeah. kid. What is it?
We need to have a conversation
about you and my aunt!
[♪♪♪]
Beck. report!
I need a response.
Something quick and decisive.
"It's all the Elementals.
They're merged
into something..."
...into something else.
Something more powerful.
It's drawing energy
from the Earth's core.
See. now.
that's some bullshit.
[SIGHS]
Is that...?
[♪♪♪]
Be ready for anything.
Yeah.
It's not real.
it's not real. it's not real!
[PANTING]
Whoa.
That's awesome.
[GRUNTING]
William. I've got drones
breaking formation.
Maybe they hit a flock of birds.
You're fine.
I wanna see what's happening
Taking manual control.
WILLIAM:
Do you see anything?
Yeah.
And I'm gonna kill him.
PETER:
I hope this works.
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
You got me?
I got you.
WILLIAM: Boss.
the illusion is coming apart.
[♪♪♪]
I see you.
[GRUNTING]
- EDITH. give me protection.
- EDITH: Copy.
[GRUNTS]
[COUGHING]
Just kill the illusion.
Kill it.
I'm not gonna. They'll see.
They'll see
what I want them to see!
- Do you still need the cape?
- Yes. Janice.
- I still need the cape.
- Done.
- Now render my illusion suit.
- All right. hang on.
The monster was full of drones!
It's crazy!
There you are.
Easy.
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
Who the hell is that?
[ALL CLAMORING]
- Ned!
- NED: Happy!
I gotta get you out of here!
- Get on the jet!
- Who are you?
I work with Spider-Man.
Get on that jet.
You work for Spider-Man?
I work with Spider-Man.
not for Spider-Man.
- New plan. Into the Tower.
- STUDENTS: What?
Happy. are you okay?
HAPPY:
We're okay. Just get Beck.
- EDITH. target Spider-Man.
- EDITH: Copy.
[♪♪♪]
I'll just kill the kids
myself.
Whoa!
There you are.
Into the Crown Jewels vault!
- Yeah. go. go. go!
- Come on.
- FLASH: Go!
- HAPPY: Into the vault!
The walls are 8 feet thick.
Go into the vault!
- What?
- Into the vault. Go!
[ALL CLAMORING]
HAPPY:
Take cover!
[BOTH PANTING]
[♪♪♪]
[PANTING]
[SOFTLY]
Okay.
Yeah?
[MOUTHS]
No. No.
[GASPS]
I see you.
Get that thing out...
[GRUNTS]
Go!
[YELLS]
How does Cap do that?
Happy. say something.
to let me know you're alive!
- HAPPY: I'm here. I'm here.
- Happy. thank God.
I bought us some time.
but not much.
I'm trying to get to Beck.
but I can't shake these drones!
[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTS]
Gotcha.
[GRUNTING]
[GRUNTS]
[PANTING]
Going up!
[GRUNTS]
[GROANS]
Finally.
Hey. William. how we doing?
Illusion almost back up.
I don't know
how you're gonna spin this.
[GRUNTING]
[PANTING]
Oh. great. No webs.
- Are we gonna die?
- Nobody dies on my watch.
I wasted my life
playing video games.
and we're gonna die.
I have a fake ID.
and I've never even used it.
I post stupid videos daily
for people to like me.
Hey. if it wasn't
for those stupid videos.
Spider-Man would've never
found you.
Spider-Man...? Spider-Man
follows me? I saved us. guys.
If you saved us.
why are we about to die?
- MJ!
- Stop it!
I'm sorry. okay?
I'm obsessed
with telling the truth
even if it hurts
other people's feelings.
I'm in love
with Spider-Man's aunt.
We're sharing. right?
[♪♪♪]
- Your lies are over. Beck.
- [GROANS]
This certainly isn't ideal.
but I have contingencies.
EDITH?
[COUGHING]
Just give me the glasses.
You want these?
Come and get them.
[INHALES DEEPLY]
Come on. Peter-tingle.
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
[GRUNTING]
Why aren't
these drones firing?
EDITH:
You're in the strike zone.
- The chance of getting hit is...
- No. fire all the drones now!
[GROANS]
[GRUNTING]
Beck!
[PANTING]
Beck.
You lied to me.
- And I trusted you.
- I know.
That's the most...
d-disappointing part.
You're a good person.
Peter.
Such a weakness.
Stark was right.
You do deserve them.
[♪♪♪]
[PANTING]
You can't trick me anymore.
EDITH.
turn off the drones.
EDITH: Biometric scan complete.
Welcome back. Peter.
Execute
all cancellation protocols?
Just do it.
- Execute them all.
- Confirmed.
[♪♪♪]
Give me the spear.
That's a halberd. Ahem.
[CHUCKLES]
Thank you.
- How could you do all of this?
- You'll see. Peter.
People.
they need to believe.
And nowadays...
they'll believe anything.
[♪♪♪]
Is he...?
Is this real?
EDITH:
All illusions are down. Peter.
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
FLASH:
Whoo! Yeah!
Hey. where you going?
[SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE]
[GRUNTING]
- MJ.
- Hey.
- Are you okay?
- I'm okay. Are you okay?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Is everybody else okay?
- Yeah. everyone's okay.
- [EXHALES]
- What happened?
- There was just the drones.
and they were following us.
and then they just stopped.
- Was that you?
- Yeah.
Did you get him?
- Well. I. um...
brought that.
In case
you needed some help.
- Thanks.
- [CHUCKLES]
Anyway. uh.
there was this sweaty guy
in the tower with us.
I think he works for you
or something.
He. um...
He gave me this.
No. No.
Oh. MJ. I'm so sorry.
- I had this stupid plan.
- Peter.
I wrote it down.
I was gonna buy you this
and give it to you in Paris
at the top...
And you kissed me.
- What? What?
- Yeah.
I don't really have
much luck
when it comes
to getting close to people.
Um... So I lied.
I wasn't just watching you
because I thought
you were Spider-Man.
[CHUCKLES]
That's great.
- Black dahlia. like the murder.
- The murder.
- Good.
- Yeah. Heh.
Sorry it's broken.
I actually like it better
broken.
[CHUCKLING]
I really like you.
I really like you too.
Uh...
[♪♪♪]
- Uh. Okay. I should...
- [CHUCKLES]
I should probably get back
to the class.
I'll go and...
- Yeah. Heh. I don't know.
- Heh. Okay.
Just in case.
[CHUCKLES]
HAPPY:
Yeah. no.
No. May. you're right.
He did great. He was strong.
Yeah.
I'm glad he stayed too.
I gotta go.
I'm glad you're alive.
I guess the coded message
worked.
"Appearances can be
deceiving." Heh.
I'm surprised you didn't
just wink in the camera.
- It worked.
- Because I had serious doubts
about Beck
from the beginning.
Not true.
He had zero doubts.
Where's Parker?
He's with a girl.
I need to speak with him.
He'll call you.
He'll...?
[LAUGHING]
Okay. Great.
Well. he better.
Or it's your ass.
And don't even think
about ghosting me.
[♪♪♪]
♪ Hey. little girl ♪
♪ I wanna be
Your boyfriend ♪
♪ Sweet little girl... ♪
[ALL SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
Are you sure
no one else has figured it out?
Yeah. it's not like anybody
really pays attention to you.
Ouch.
Except for me.
Aw. Thanks.
- Don't be late.
- I won't.
See you later.
- You guys are so cute.
- Thanks.
Uh...
I was thinking we should all go
on a double date or something.
[IN UNISON]
Oh. we broke up.
No. What? Why?
Men and women
grow apart.
but the journey
they share together
will always be a part
of them.
- You are so wise.
- Thank you.
Hello. Gerald.
Could Mother not make it?
Hmm.
- PETER: May!
- I promise you... Ah!
Oh. he's here.
Don't give me a ticket.
- Heh. Ah.
- Ooh. I'm so glad you're okay.
No. for real. I'm good.
I'm actually really fine.
Let's go.
Where are your bags?
Oh. right.
They got blown up.
Yeah. Heh.
I got you
hot buttered bagels.
- Thank you so much.
- I know my boy.
PETER: I kept my
identity pretty guarded
this past couple years.
I faced a lot of deception.
And I'm tired of the lies.
So it's time for the truth
to be out there.
Are you dating?
- Yes.
- Not really.
- What?
- Well...
- I think...
- Summer fling.
Yes. that evolves
and grows like any other.
I still don't know
where it's going.
Open to wherever
it might lead.
- Anywhere. On or off.
- To share it with people...
We'll always be friends.
no matter what.
I'm gonna go
because I've got a date.
HAPPY: ...because we
all are interconnected.
- Bye.
- MAY: We are.
[♪♪♪]
Whoo!
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
[THUDDING]
Sorry!
Whoa!
Whoa.
Whoo!
Whoo-hoo!
- Hey.
- Hey. Sorry I'm late.
- It's fine.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
- You're gonna love this.
Okay! Okay!
- Okay. Okay.
- You ready?
Yeah. I'm just not gonna watch.
I'm not gonna watch.
[MJ WHIMPERING]
I should stop looking.
I'm gonna stop looking! Heh.
PETER:
Whoo!
[MJ SCREAMING]
[♪♪♪]
♪ Can't seem to get my mind
Off of you ♪
♪ Back here at home
There's nothing to do ♪
♪ Ooh. ooh ♪
♪ Now that I'm away ♪
♪ I wish I'd stayed ♪
♪ Tomorrow's a day of mine
That you won't be in ♪
♪ When you looked at me
I should've run ♪
♪ But I thought
It was just for fun ♪
♪ I see I was wrong ♪
♪ And I'm not so strong ♪
♪ I should've known all along
That time would tell ♪
♪ A week without you
Thought I'd forget ♪
♪ Two weeks without you ♪
♪ And I still haven't gotten
Over you yet ♪
♪ Vacation
All I ever wanted ♪
Had to get away ♪
♪ Vacation
Meant to be spent alone ♪
All I ever wanted ♪
♪ Vacation
Had to get away ♪
Meant to be spent alone ♪
♪ Vacation
All I ever wanted ♪
Had to get away ♪
♪ Vacation
Meant to be spent alone ♪
Okay. You can put me down now!
You can put me down now!
PETER:
You okay?
Uh...
Whoo! Yeah. Yeah. I'm okay.
Let's just...
Never. never doing that again.
- I'm never doing that again.
- Okay.
I should probably
get out of here.
- Be safe. Heh.
- See you later.
MAN [OVER LED SCREEN]:
This is breaking news.
We come with revelations about
last week's attack in London.
An anonymous source
provided this video.
It shows Quentin Beck.
aka Mysterio.
moments before his death.
A warning. you may find
this video disturbing.
I managed to send the Elemental
through the rift.
but I don't think
I'm gonna make it.
Spider-Man attacked me
for some reason.
He has an army of weaponized
drones. Stark technology.
saying he's the only one who's
gonna be the new Iron Man.
EDITH: Are you sure you want
to commence the drone attack?
There will be
significant casualties.
PETER:
Do it. Execute them all.
[GUNS FIRING]
This shocking video
was released earlier today
on the controversial
news website
TheDailyBugle.net.
There you have it. folks.
conclusive proof
that Spider-Man
was responsible
for the murder of Mysterio.
an interdimensional warrior
who gave his life
to protect our planet
and who will no doubt
go down in history
as the greatest superhero
of all time.
But that's not all. folks.
Here's the real blockbuster.
Brace yourselves.
You might wanna sit.
Spider-Man's real...
Spider-Man's real name is...
Spider-Man's name
is Peter Parker.
What the fu...?
[♪♪♪]
[SKA SONG
PLAYING OVER RADIO]
♪ Stop
Your messing around ♪
♪ Better think
Of your future... ♪
You gotta tell him.
It was fine.
The little boy
handled it.
We helped.
- Talos.
- Come off it.
How was I supposed to know
that the whole thing
was fake?
I mean. that was all
very. very convincing.
The performances.
the illusion.
that costume.
the craftsmanship in that.
This is just embarrassing
for a shape-shifter. Fine.
Hey there. I hope your mission
is going well.
We gave the glasses to Parker
about a week ago. like you said.
And it was very touching.
you know?
Really. really
quite touching.
Talos.
Um... And. you know.
shortly after that.
it really kind of went
off the rails.
so we need you to come back.
Everyone kept asking
where the Avengers are.
I don't know
what to say to that.
so you're lucky
that Spider-Man won...
[SEAGULLS SQUAWKING]
[EXHALES]
[GRUNTS]
[♪♪♪]
Everybody back to work!
Who's got my shoes?
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org